https://todayshomeowner.com/privacy-policy/

Guest Submissions
Subscribe!
Privacy Policy
Welcome to the Today’s Homeowner with Danny Lipford website, located at https://todayshomeowner.com, and operated by Remodeling Today, Inc.
This Privacy Policy will inform you about how Remodeling Today collects and uses your personally identifiable information, or PII, and other information in operating the Website.
How does the Website Work?
The Website offers anonymous visitors the ability to learn about Remodeling Today’s products, and visitors who are at least eighteen (18) years of age and who register with the Website can purchase our products.
By using the Website, you consent to the collection and use of your information by Remodeling Today as described herein.
Remodeling Today reserves the right to change how we handle the information we collect through the Website at any time.
We will update this Privacy Policy to reflect any changes in our privacy collection and handling practices, and such changes will take effect immediately once posted to the Website.
What type of personally identifiable information does Remodeling Today collect from you and how do we use it?
Registrants must provide certain personally identifiable information (“PII”) to Remodeling Today to purchase our products and participate in mailing lists, polls, surveys and sweepstakes from time to time.
Such PII includes basic biographical information, such as your name, phone number, and email address. We may also ask you for general statistical information about yourself and your interests.
In addition, we use cookies that collect information about your computer and web browsing habits on https://todayshomeowner.com so we can understand visitors’ content and advertising preferences.
How will we use your personally identifiable information?
Remodeling Today will use your PII to: register you for contests; personalize your user experience; respond to questions and comments you send to us; send you marketing information such as emails, newsletters and other items that we believe would interest you; and help us analyze visitors’ content preferences to help us improve the website.
We may provide your PII to entities who work on our behalf or with us. These entities may use your PII to help fulfill your requests in connection with the Website and to help us communicate with you about different resources offered as part of the Website.
For instance, we may transfer information submitted by you, including PII, to service providers and other third parties who assist us in running the Website and to third-party vendors in order to execute transactions requested by you.
Under what other circumstances may we release PII?
We may also release your PII if we believe such release is necessary to comply with the law (e.g., a legal process or a statutory authorization), to apply or enforce our customer agreements, to fulfill our obligations as a result of a merger, acquisition or like event with another entity or individual, to protect our rights or property, to protect Registrants and/or Visitors from fraudulent, abusive, or unlawful use of the Website, or if we reasonably believe that a danger to any person requires disclosure of such PII.
What other information does Remodeling Today collect?
We also collect anonymous and aggregate information from you about your preferences in navigating the Website by using cookies, action tags and other methods.
Cookies are small text files that identify your computer. We may use cookies to, among other things, monitor Website usage, customize Website features, identify your computer’s operating system and browser, and complete transactions.
An action tag is a small, graphic image on a webpage that is designed to allow the website owner or a third party to monitor who is visiting a website by collecting the IP address of the computer to which the tag is sent, the URL of the webpage that the tag comes from and the time that such webpage was viewed.
Tags may be associated with cookie information. We may also use such anonymous and aggregate information for promotional purposes.
Do I have the ability not to be identified by Remodeling Today?
Yes. If you do not want to be identified by us, you can set your browser to warn you before accepting cookies and refuse cookies when your browser alerts you to their presence. You can also adjust the settings in your browser to refuse all cookies.
If you do not want us to have any of your PII, do not submit any of your PII to us.
Please read our complete Cookies Policy for more information.
How do we store information?
Remodeling Today takes steps consistent with commercially reasonable industry standards to secure any PII collected from you from loss, misuse, unauthorized access and destruction while under our control.
Please note that despite our efforts to protect information provided to us, we cannot guarantee that such information will not be lost, disclosed or accessed by accidental circumstances or by the unauthorized acts of others.
Does Remodeling Today provide links to other websites?
Remodeling Today may provide links to other websites or resources of possible interest to you. Because we have no control over such websites or resources, the collection and use of your PII and other information by such websites shall be subject to the policies and procedures of such websites and not this Privacy Policy.
What are our policies regarding children?
You must be eighteen (18) years of age or older in order to purchase our products. Remodeling Today does not knowingly collect PII from anyone under sixteen (16) years of age.
Who is your data controller (under the General Data Protection Regulation)?
Our data controller is Today’s Homeowner Media, whose physical address is 75 Midtown Park East, Mobile, AL, 36606. You can contact the controller at 251-478-3345 or email webmaster@dannylipford.com.
Is providing PII mandatory to use this Website?
Providing personally identifiable information is not mandatory to view articles or videos on the Website. However, entering your PII is necessary to enter contests, giveaways, purchase items from the store or to comment on the Website.
Do you use PII to make automated decisions?
We do not use your PII to make automated decisions.
Do we have a mechanism to address the removal of PII and complaints about the handling of information that we collect?
If you wish to remove PII that you have submitted to Remodeling Today, please send us an email requesting such removal to webmaster@dannylipford.com.
If you have questions or concerns about any of our information collection or handling practices, please contact us at webmaster@dannylipford.com.
Subscribe!
© 2020 Today’s Homeowner Media. All rights reserved. Reproduction in whole or in part without permission is prohibited.
